// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " I am not really interested in others",
    answer: " Neutral",
    options: [
      " strongly Agree",
      " Agree",
      "Neutral",
      " disagree",
      "strongly disagree"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "I know how to comfort others ",
    answer: "strongly Agree",
    options: [
      " strongly Agree",
      " Agree",
      "Neutral",
      " disagree",
      "strongly disagree"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "I feel others' emotions",
    answer: "Agree",
    options: [
      " strongly Agree",
      " Agree",
      "Neutral",
      " disagree",
      "strongly disagree"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: " I take an interest in other people's lives ",
    answer: " disagree",
    options: [
      " strongly Agree",
      " Agree",
      "Neutral",
      " disagree",
      "strongly disagree"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "I cheer people up ",
    answer: "strongly agree",
    options: [
      " strongly Agree",
      " Agree",
      "Neutral",
      " disagree",
      "strongly disagree"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "I make people feel at ease ",
    answer: "Neutral",
    options: [
      " strongly Agree",
      " Agree",
      "Neutral",
      " disagree",
      "strongly disagree"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: " I take time out for others ",
    answer: " Agree",
    options: [
      " strongly Agree",
      " Agree",
      "Neutral",
      " disagree",
      "strongly disagree"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 8,
    question: " I don't like to get involved in other people's problems ",
    answer: "Neutral",
    options: [
      " strongly Agree",
      " Agree",
      "Neutral",
      " disagree",
      "strongly disagree"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "  I am not really interested in others  ",
    answer: " disagree",
    options: [
      " strongly Agree",
      " Agree",
      "Neutral",
      " disagree",
      "strongly disagree"
    ]
  },


 
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];